

A.J.Jubairi@gmail.com



+966544454140

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

An ambitious and result – driven Master-level management and business studies professional with skills and experience in areas such as project management, change management, new venture development and corporate social responsibility and sustainability. I possess a strong ability in conducting market research and have led and overseen multiple projects. Have maintained high standards of service, work ethics and communication with advanced knowledge of scheduling, meeting facilitation, and creation of policies and procedures inline with business goal. I thrive on challenges presented to me and can work in high pressure situations, both in team based and individual environment.

EDUCATION

MASTER OF MANAGEMENT

2018

Massey University, Auckland, New Zealand

Modules: Project Management; Organisation & Management; Business & Sustainability; Leading & Changing.

GRADUATE DIPLOMA IN BUSINESS STUDIES 2016-2017

Massey University, Auckland, New Zealand

Modules: International Business; Manging Services; Cross-Cultural Communication; Contemporary management; Manging Human resource.

CAREER SUMMARY

CUSTOMER ASSISTANT 2017

New World Supermarket, Part-Time During my study.

- Gained significant work and cultural experience after first moving to New Zealand
- Developed understanding of the New Zealand workplace while adjusting to the new location
- Provided customers with superior service through attentive communication and active listening

OFFICE ADMINISTRATOR 2012 – 2

Ministry of Education, Riyadh.

- Provided administrative support to managers and staff members assisting with daily office needs
- Answered and directed all phone calls and queries to relevant departments
- Maintained in-depth schedules involving organising and scheduling appointments
- Planned and participated in meetings while taking detailed notes and minutes
- Ensured support to all guests, clients, and visitors while providing superior customer service

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE 2010-2011

Hollandi Bank, Jeddah.

- · Developed and maintained consistent and reliable customer service at all times to promote retention and client satisfaction
- · Ensured all customers receive detailed information on products including loans and credit cards
- Answered all guest queries or referred them to relevant departments
- De-escalated situations and resolved escalated issues in a timely manner while maintaining empathy and understanding

VOLUNTEER WORK

COORDINATOR

ALBANY STUDENTS' ASSOCIATION 2016-2017

- Planning, organizing, and managing events
- Delegating duties to team members
- Responsible in the data recording and files ensuring confidentially
- Assessing requirements, managing procurement and archiving processes

RELEVANT SKILLS & INFO

IT: Mac and PC operating systems, Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook)

SKILLS: Management – Conduct research – Team leader – Learning & Development

INTERESTS

Keeping track of the latest management and business, theories and practices by following up the most useful sites.

REFERENCES

Available on request